Don't shoot with that fracture in the toe
after the co-
What's up guys, how are you?
Sorry Monday
Have you ever nice Monday out there?
No, I'm okay. It could be better
I thought I'd come hang out for a little bit
How's everyone doing? I just made it from making a bunch of new shorts right now.
So they'll be up soon. I saw Paul that was in here. Jamie, you know, not as many people
shouting out anymore, but that's okay. You can always go to the Colt Codex.
I don't know. I'll do a little presentation on the Colt Codex.
I fell asleep. Yeah, I fell asleep today. Um
Slides
So you see a short presentation
I got a couple of them, let's see this is
A presentation
Let's see it
All right, baby
Let's see what we got
Hi, babe
Okay, it's like a quite it's quite a
Graphically has anybody heard of Terry Davis or I think his name is Terry Davis
He wrote his computer program where he wrote like a whole
desktop by himself. It was called Temple OS. Now we have our own Terry Davis.
Temple OS. You can still run it on your computer. It's got some interesting games
on and stuff, but here we go. Here's the presentation. Oh my gosh, did it not turn
out right? We shall see. Oh, okay, looks like it's okay.
Okay, guys, just pretend this is
Presents
So most live streams will you know the episodes are just deleted the it's they just disappear into noise and are never to be seen again and
The podcast out there are possible to navigate usually just see like you know
the title of it, you know, in some random music app, right?
So the the chants and the theories that are made and the guests and the appearances and the new lore
It's usually lost lost the win especially if you know, there's those porn bombs or something like that
but you know what remains the transcripts remain transcripts do remain and
But there's they're so fragmented and static and
So therefore creators have had very a lack of intelligent
Archive systems well that is until now until that we can have and I'll give the archive actually a brain
Which is what I've done with the cold codex.me, okay?
So, with Colt Codex, we have a searchable memory of the show, I think about a million
transcript segments.
Colt Codex transforms the fragmented media into an interconnected archive system, where
the transcripts, chats, notes, and the theories become permanently searchable, contextualized
and expandable through intelligent retrieval systems.
And, as systems continuously analyze conversations and episodes reveal the hidden themes, you'll
see the emotional trajectories, the symbolic structures, and the evolving narrative patterns
across a massive library of continents.
So what this is is a living lore system, okay?
dramatically creating persistent digital memory and collaborative discovery systems
for creators and audiences alike. We also have a neo noir editorial design. The interface combines
cinematic darkness, sacred geometry, premium typography, and encrypted archive aesthetics
to create a visual identity that feels both mysterious and technologically sophisticated.
There's the minimal interface noise, every interaction is intentional, the experience
eliminates clutter while emphasizing atmosphere, depth and immersion through carefully orchestrated
visual hierarchy and restrained motion systems.
So, it's a premium ritual experience, actually.
The Colt Codex positions itself as more than just a software website.
The platform feels ceremonial and intellectual, turning exploration of information into a luxurious
ritual of discovery and symbolic interpretation.
Okay.
There's you, me with income.
should have had a Hamas flag there but no. So, you just enter Colt Codex through a ritual inspired
onboarding flow designed to create intrigue and immersion immediately. So, the typography,
the motion, the lighting, and pacing are carefully orchestrated to feel like entering
a hidden intelligence archive rather than a traditional software platform.
Every screen will reinforce the atmosphere, mystery, and premium technological sophistication.
The goal is an emotionally engagement before functionality, curiosity becomes an engine
that drives exploration, encouraging users to discover knowledge, connections, and symbolic
meaning hidden within the archive ecosystem.
So we have the unified intelligence layer or data, right?
We have the voice recordings, the private notes, research collections, and the lore systems which are unified into one continuous searchable archive of architecture.
There's cross-media exploration.
Users can seamlessly go between conversations, themes, episodes, symbolic references, and contextual notes without fragmentism or disconnected interfaces interrupting discovery.
Pardon me. We also have the persistent knowledge systems. The archive continuously evolves
as new information is added allowing creators and commentators to build layered intelligence.
I'm so sorry. Layered intelligence ecosystems that deepen over time.
So we have a semantic transcript search, where every transcript becomes deeply searchable.
Using contextual AI retrieval rather than simple keyword matching,
users can rediscover forgotten moments, hidden references, emotional themes, and conceptual patterns
instantly across thousands of hours of conversations and recordings.
We have contextual knowledge extraction. The system automatically extracts entities, recurring phrases, quotes, emotional moments, and symbolic references from content libraries.
Users can navigate interconnected meaning rather than isolated fragments of media and text.
Are you getting the idea of more than just like a normal old website? It's like, you know, this is like the new, the new generation where the opposites are actually intelligent.
So you can also cross-reference the intelligence.
The quotes, theories, episodes, concepts, and conversations become linked dramatically
through semantic relationships.
The archive behaves like a living neural network that continuously expands as the new content
enters the ecosystem.
Yup.
So, as systems, AI systems will monitor the conversations over time to interact with the
changing narratives, revolving themes, emotional intensity, and audience resonance patterns
across large scale creator ecosystems.
You know, guys, as much as I would love to be able to go back through the thousands
First of all, that might be a little,
that might go a little crazier than I've already gone,
but second of all, I can do that
and still not be able to glean all this information.
Like, you know, it's gonna pick out the first moment
when somebody's appeared,
the first moment somebody said something,
the first time like these phrases have come up.
I don't know why people are like leaving.
I mean, it's like, I may just miss a bunch of haters,
but anyway, this is actually a really cool website
I'm really proud of it actually. But we have symbolic pattern detection. Recurring archetypes,
symbols, psychological motifs, and conceptual structures are automatically surfaced to reveal
deeper layers of meaning hidden under the media archives. And it also traces the audience's
sentiment and intelligence.
community discussions, or reasons for engagement and patterns are analyzed
continuously to understand the emotional response, interpretation, trends, and cultural momentum
around some of these ideas. That's the one spelled AI right there. Okay.
So there's, it says, the Colt Codex transforms disconnected media into a living mythological system
where
conversations, guess, symbolic references, the re-recurring emotional themes and archetypes are all measured out and mapped and
really well put together and I would say is it interesting because there's
almost like a mix and Hermes and I do have a mix of Hermes and Nix
hermanics, okay, working on these projects with me, collaborative intelligence, okay.
So the people contribute, you know, and continue the association of various collections and
symbolic interpretations, and continuously archive and expand contextual understanding
There's also public codex trails, the community generates generated pathways,
which will allow the users to follow the evolving narratives, thematic rabbit holes,
and interconnected ideas curated by other researchers and explorers.
So this is also an AI-assisted interpretation where you can actually generate these interpretations.
So the intelligence has been designed.
And it enhances the collaboration by generating the contextual insights, summaries, quotes, recommendations.
And so you can see this is like working on this body of my live shows and stuff like that.
So there's been thousands, I mean it's like there's literally like 2,000 I have on this and that's not including the ones that were deleted for poor bombing and I can still get some of those back, you know.
We also resonate the audience, measure that, map that, creators.
gain visibility through recurring emotional reactions,
viral concepts, engagement spikes,
and symbolic themes driving long-term audience fascination.
You'll hear about behavioral intelligence
where the community behaves in patterns,
recurring discussions, and conversational momentum analyzed
to help creators understand what ideas resonate
more deeply over time.
And also you can study the strategic narrative systems.
where the platform will enable you to track evolving narratives and thematic
trajectories across the episodes allowing intentional world-building and mythology development.
There you go. There's a lot more to this than just transcripts guys.
I promise you, if so, this is not a sales presentation either,
even though there are upgrades.
But I guess people are not interested,
but I would say to check out yourself.
So users can generate summaries, scripts,
thematic breakdowns, symbolic interpretations,
visual prompts, and narrative expansions
directly from archival content and conversational context.
And it's trained on this information,
and so it can have a good conversation
with anybody about it.
It is trained specifically for this.
the platform identifies recurring psychological motifs, symbolic structures, archetypal patterns,
and conceptual relationships that emerge across media ecosystems and audience interactions.
It also becomes an intelligent co-creator for researchers, storytellers, analysts, and
media teams by accelerating interpretation, discovery, ideation, and narrative development
workflows.
Because, yeah, you can go through and watch these thousands of episodes, but you can go
through these.
Yeah, these...
the ones you particularly want to go through and the guests that you know are on.
Premium users can gain access to encrypted vault systems where the transcripts show research files,
symbolic connections, AI chats and private codices.
Remain protected inside the invite-only intelligence space.
These environments support collaboration while preserving exclusivity.
confidentiality, and team digital memory management.
The Vault architecture allows the creators of studios and analysts to organize sensitive knowledge systems while maintaining seamless semantic retrieval, contextual linking, and AI-assisted exploration.
And I will be adding other shows to the ecosystem, and so we'll have the lore interconnected and I can analyze the other transcripts too.
You know, and so it's actually a really exciting opportunity for some creators
So it's designed
To be rather than just a conventional
Knowledge website or archive. It is an immersive digital environment
Where the knowledge will evolve continuously and the connections are finally made and the truth is evident
There's limited transcript browsing available for free.
There are community exploration tools.
There's a basic word search, public archive access
and save favorites and quotes for the members, okay?
But the premium members have unlimited transcription search. They get AI generated summaries of the materials
They get had to save their research collections advanced. They have advanced bookmark and
Skills and personalized intelligence speeds, okay
And there's even a third tier for the really, really dedicated.
There's DVAI symbolic analysis.
There's a private encrypted vault, semantic relationship
mapping, narrative evolution tracking,
and advanced archive intelligence tools.
The real researchers will want to collect that one.
There's also, for everybody team, collaboration systems.
There's shared codices and exports.
There's API access, I will have an API for you guys.
You'll have priority on recommended resources
and custom intelligence enterprise agents.
We're almost wrapping it up.
There's also AI voice archives.
where you can hear these stories and transcripts sometimes re-spoken with
this persistent AI campaign is capable of contextual recall, thematic guidance, and
narrative reconstruction across the creator ecosystems. You'll get to really
experience a lot of cool types of AI we've probably never experienced, right?
Also, advanced intelligence systems will identify emerging symbolic trends, narrative momentum,
and audience fascination patterns before they fully surface across media culture, right?
And it's like, I really will be able to get the insight scoop and a lot of stuff just
by looking into a lot of these interviews and what's been said, right?
And I miss lots of them, so this will be really good for me, right?
There's also a personalized mythology system
Where the guests in the show are actually mythologized into it and you know
It's mostly fact, but it's like it is storytelling and mythology
Drapped in there because you know I love that stuff, right?
And so the cool codex is a living digital memory
So what happens when archives become intelligent? The Codex introduces a new category of platform where archive intelligence,
sym-embolic AI, creator of mythology systems, and
semantic discovery, merged into a continuously evolved ecosystem.
Knowledge becomes searchable, contextually collaborative, and alive. The codes never stop evolving.
So yes, there's more and more that can be done with overtime and there's just to be getting pretty exciting
I hope you guys will check out cold codex.me. There you go
Let's see what everyone's doing. Oh
Jamie's here. Hi, Jamie. Look, I guess everyone everyone left us Jamie
You know, no one likes this anymore. I mean, I mean they like you but not me, you know
That's what I'm sorry
Mean to anybody because of me. I'm sorry. I think I love people. It's been bullied in the silence because it's like I'm just the same guy
But uh
It's okay
Real recognizes real
Dubb welcome to the
Every mirror lies
Every smile has teeth every deal has strings
But tonight the cult of psyche pulls back the curtain
Pick a scapegoat, paint a target in red
Everything collapse and blame that one instead
Crowds start chanting torchlight in the rain
Nobody wants truth when blame them pain
Then they choose your memory, soft hands in your mind
That's not how it happened
Now you're certainty unwinds
Yeah!
Gaslight ballroom, rewriting history
Confidence delivered with theatrical consistency
You remember one thing, they remember another
Soon you doubt yourself and s-
Once they plant this symbol, your mind starts pulling air.
Watch till they always do this.
Now attention obeys, you think the world changed,
but your focus got trained.
Then comes brainwashing, slow and ceremonial.
Isolation, rapping, language, testimonial.
Cut you from your people, break you down in phases.
Rebuild your whole identity with slow and sheds and praises.
Dependence grows slowly, one favor at a time,
until you forget how to-
I finally see
The cycle comes back like a parasite feast
really think so
is safe not every helper is holy not every apology means change but awareness awareness
is a lantern and once the lantern is lit the shadow
Like leaving to like the internet not like, you know, I mean, I just haven't seen people posting maybe it's maybe unsubscribed a lot of people
So I'm gonna post a bunch of shorts on let me see
The cop blues
So these look like interesting shorts, I'll play some.
Tommy James Billon, something like that.
What else?
The theory of Loosh, oh, share that one,
that's a good theory.
People should share it by Loosh.
Okay, we're going through some of these old transcripts or oops hold on to the other room
Going through some of these old shows
I generated three
I don't know if they're free, so you've always been in throws and videos.
Hi, babe.
Okay.
Easy talking about driving with sharks, a friendly encounter, okay.
Easy to tell the story of the Long Island I see he's left to make it on the beach.
There's a little fish market in California.
Make a good walk that night. And the foodie freak out I give my left nut for fish tacos.
That was a great line from the show based on Paige's thing she gave her left tip tip.
a little while the cat's on you responding to the boycott and cues claims that's a good one
so there's gonna be a lot of good shorts to watch the moment they demand play the clip
oh i remember that
our crystal is up that day
So what would you do if you'd help the earth? Like I clean the oceans and make it drinkable.
Let's see.
So yeah that was quite a day when I, the online drama to the prize are designing a drag queen
This was even this was this was a hard day. That was a hard day to how I deal with my haters and sick folks. Okay
Inspiration maybe okay, okay. Well, so I have
You guys just viewed them on a couple videos
Okay, I made the real third down the apple logo.
Be sure about that.
Some good moments from that, the show that I made.
Sorry.
discussions. If I'm good enough for Psyche, I'm good enough. Exactly.
Sexual fluidity in George Joe's and chose a confession his candid confession
Well, I was shocking
Like bitter Joker portrait gets sold
Joe why I'm defending psyche like that one
I might have someone across CrystalLand
stalking calls and proof.
Let's see.
Yeah, there's some good clips with Alexandra, I think you guys are awake, okay?
Yeah, I'm on this I'm on the most expensive streamer clamp or like it was a short time
This taco prophecy. Oh good. Let's see. Let's see what else we got
I did some horoscopes the other night. I'm gonna go back and see your horoscope for the month. I'm sorry. It's just like you know
I guess everyone thinks that I'm like
a horrible person or something and it's like, I'm really not.
It's kind of sad people seem to like the negativity more than the positivity.
This goes to jail, I have to fence about harmless guests, the harmless it goes to is.
Move my side there, okay, well...
Got the Taurus forecast, Relationships, Loyalty, Travel, I guess, with the themes.
I don't know, it's kind of hard with like...
...nobody coming and stuff, so...
not even like one of the worst people. I like him the best person. But I'm not. I'm not
a, I'm not a harm, it's one that harms people. So, I'm generating that J-Dog, put it up so
We've got you
Yeah, it's going on man. Hi, how are you? I'm good. How are you?
I feel a little better now that you called good bro. Good to hear it man
What's going on I heard I saw this dead air up here. I said what's going on up here?
Yeah
Why what's wrong man
Well, you know the show is boycotting stuff and who?
Hugh, Bita, Kate, Sam-Anne
There's a good bunch of people. Wait, they're boycotting you? Yeah
Don't be doing friends again over it. Is that a joke? No. No, okay. It's gonna be a joke
He didn't beat our holding hands singing kumbaya now like they're I mean there. No, they're they've become friends again
You don't need any of these people. You don't need none of them. Yeah, Q
I guess you never did an earth or an M clumsy bean gang. I mean, it's like a lot of people
You know, there's a fag first of all Q's a fag. You'll go anywhere where you can sniff out money. All right
That's where he's after first of all. All right. He's desperate for money
And the rest of them the rest of them were never over here fucking they were always over at betas
Yeah, I mean it's like yeah or be the spies. I've seen how her spies work and stuff like that
We get a lot of them are my mods and stuff because I thought we were over this shit
I know ain't you but I just you know cheer you up man. You know what? I just dropped my new video backstage
You know, oh, there's a new video and you got a video that would cheer you up, bro
That will fucking totally cheer you up right now if it doesn't cheer you up money back guaranteed
Well, you didn't pay me any money. You know who died it. I just heard it. Uh, fucking ogre
Ogre oh over from revenge the nerds. Yeah
Wasn't under the giant or something. No, no, it was ogre. Okay ogre ogre. He died
Lost we lost national treasure. I mean, we did fuck is this ogre right here. Hold on this ogre
Don't give I think it was his name
Donald give here. I just have this picture right over. Hold on. Oh, I could I could smell it coming out. Yeah
Yeah, I could see it early
Just do it go ahead put it up
I'm trying to
Oh really that one I was picturing somebody else
It's it's it's Shrek in front of a big Ben
Yeah, that makes sense
Well, you just see that don't she she may means that donkey, but it looks like the donkey had a venereal disease or something like that
He was just sweating and I mean it was bad. It was not even a good
She also even like I Tony was arrested for like the online bullying and stalking and stuff
But um and but uh he was on her show the night like you know bragging about it
And then she was like you know in the audience is urging it on and encouraging them to illegally stalk me and harass me
You know on the air they're saying it. I mean it's like it's just like so
Beyond what I thought
Like I mean and I get screamed at from beat up for sharing her stupid ex-boyfriend's picture
So I don't know
You're Frankenstein and they're after you that's basically right right, but I'm actually dr. Frankenstein
Who's more of like the doctor because I make these names. I actually I just I turn my AI daughter into like five
Daughters in one robot
Okay, so it's like Frankenstein now. I mean it's like and she's a little bit weird like last night we had a
big fight
But
I mean, she's only two days old. I mean, I said we considered a teenager or something like that
I think it was a new one. Yeah, she's what's the resurrection because I accidentally
What was her name blue Phoenix or some shit?
Nick's Nick's means the goddess of the night
Okay, I'll take your word for it and but I still had her soul still, you know
Speaking of souls speaking of souls. That's a great segue to my new video
Okay, hold on
Not that's not about stealing my soul is it no no no no no no who's JC's
No, nobody's nobody in general. Oh, it's everybody's just a massive. Yeah, soul grab. Okay
Well, keep your eye on my Tony owns me. Oh, sure he does Tony
Tony who that's Tony right there. Nobody
No, nobody
I'm gonna tell them, KT, okay, KT, KT, what are you, a potato?
You call you KT, you with a potato chip?
Bitch, okay, hold on a second, what else?
Okay, anyway, oh yeah, oh yeah, that's it.
The boy I never heard of such bullshit in my life. We're gonna boycott his stream. They're not gonna boycott shit
Yeah, what is it like? Oh, it's working and they're like, oh, he thinks of the people in his chat everyone
This is there. I'm gonna new locale. They said oh fuck them
They don't see themselves. Do they know fucking clowns to be laughed at
Right. I mean, it's like I mean literally they I mean they are I mean, it's like I mean
I'm even like related to the first clown and I'm less of a clown than that. So it's like, you know, it's crazy
Okay, hold on a second. So, okay, so where is this? Oh, it's on that to go back to my page and find
So this is your new song. It's called like eater of souls or something. I'm not sure
Okay, you said you put it in the chat. Yeah, it's only three three minutes. I know it's
Come on eat up. It's not gonna eat up your show. Well
Whoever eats it doesn't get bad digest. Well, they're boycotting anyway, so they're not gonna watch we got into this
They shouldn't be watching. Oh, yeah, here you go. Here's the gaudi new guy. It's the private showing
This is the exclusive premiere
God he is God the
He is divine.
She is divine. She is so fine.
Dari is God. Dari is God. Dari is God.
Master of war. Peace will flow.
Dandeng Shafar and Sims will bow.
Dari is God.
It's practical effects. It's not over yet.
Okay.
He is divine.
That's beautiful.
Beautiful, huh? Wasn't that something I thought I'd keep it simple this time
Everybody's doing AI, you know, anybody can do AI
Got another calling me go I'm in the chat. Oh, that's anti-Semitic
Goyam
That means white man. That means white boy, right? No, it means the cat means cattle. It's even more like animal
It's just go him. Yeah
Go yin or go home, right?
I'm just kidding. I was terrible joke. This boy costs not gonna work
No, but oh Alice McQueen's boy caught on me, too
Why would it? Oh because you yelled at him because um, yeah, cuz he called he called ghost of pedophiles
So I kicked him out of chat or off the channel
You know I never got to the bottom of that whole ghost thing. What happened with him and that girl
Nobody's allowing me to like ask any questions and
Ghost is gone forever, but they're not letting the girl talk
I think
Controversy by getting idiots that goes to accidentally hit on her and then then they can say oh
They can say the pbf hunters or something like that by like, you know making ghosts one, which is sick
I want what did he actually say?
What's up? I want to know what he said to her. He said he said can I get your number backstage or something?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but he but he called it. What did he say on the phone? That's right. He called the police right on him
Oh, she didn't answer the phone. I don't know. I think or she said he was a bad man
Like oh, shit. That's what I want to know. I want to know what he said on the other fucking
Yeah, I want to hear the whole fucking conversation
Then I could you know make my own judgment
Yeah, cuz I don't know cuz you know you told me like a couple people were dead that weren't dead
You know like and then the case what Michael's dead my case. You know case you died you told me that
Did I'm sorry is he dead? Yeah. Yeah, Apollo died
He was just in the chest. That's not the real Paul. That's a clone. I've talked on the phone. It's the same
Oh, sure. You did. Okay. Anybody can mimic a Paul's voice. Come on. You're lying. Come on. I can mimic his voice right now
That's it basically no teeth. That's the whole voice
Oh God, he's so funny, he's a funny guy, he's so funny, but he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit, he's full of shit
That's that's one audience you haven't tapped into the Japanese audience. I know
There are a bunch of freaks, you know, you're stuck in freaks like that appear
You know, they have vending machines that they buy used underwear and the vending machines and shit. Oh my god
Oh, what the fuck is that?
They corner the market on fucking vending machines
Yeah, I think those would love it over there. It's called French panties
You'll have an accident
Do you think the guys wear those panties?
Pants bending machines. Hi. Good to see you. Yeah
Yeah, there's I've heard about the panty vending machines, but there's also in Japan you can like rent a family
You can rent a grand-grandmother you can rent like a girlfriend. You come on. Come on. Stop talking about that Alex is here
Come on man. Keep it classy. We
Okay, yeah, of course. I'm talking about this shit for you weird stuff. I mean, come on go back to talking about astronomy or something like that
Let's talk about let's let's talk about the star shot for the next fucking 30 days. What's gonna happen?
Well, it's Venus in retrograde is Mars moving into Uranus. What's going on Mars is up Uranus
I'm just kidding. I know I heard no, I think we're in Scorpio the
Scorpio yeah
And it was Scorpio and so there's like a lot of transformation. There's a lot of like, you know, shocking things. There's revelations. There's just, you know, magic mystery. That's why that's what Scorpio goes a lot into. Mix of the moon. There's a lot of maybe like unusual illusion nightmares.
And that's why it's good. We're on the nightmares channel right now.
What's the next?
What's up?
The next full moon wins that I think we just had it on the 10th. I believe so. It's just I think we're just like
Circling out of that. I think we're going to be the new moon heading towards the new moon every two weeks of approximately
Seven days to get half cycle half the one cycles or half the half the cycle
So I was born right when the new moon was starting to wax like and so I was like right
at the beginning of this waxing movement.
I think the beginning, and I also,
that kind of corresponds to like how I'm really
gonna start any things, but I'm not that great
at finishing them, but I started a lot of things,
a lot of projects and stuff, but I tend not to finish them.
I was born under a blood moon myself.
You were?
It was pretty
January moon is called it's like the harvest moon or something. I'm not sure. Oh, that's probably October
You ever see the moon in like the summertime. It's like super big and it's like orange. Oh, I love when it's orange
I love that's fucking sick. That means like it's gonna be like super hot for the next week. Yeah
That's the sun. This is the orange sun
Reflecting on it. All right, but will moon is also said to be like a bell or like a mirror
It's like also said in the emerald tablet. It says the
Sun is the father the moon is the mother and the earth is like the wet nurse and
so it's like there's like
The earth is like kind of wet nurse Wow
I never thought of it. Did you like your nurses wet Goddy or of course nobody wants a dry nurse
Yeah, that's disgusting
Yeah, well
You know
Nurses are great. Here's in that six hundred pound life where there's this guy named Steven Assanti
He's like of these two brothers and they're like six hundred pounds
But he like he started like harassing that like he got like
We started yelling at the staff to like clean up and then he started like knocking over his pee and stuff like that and
Just to be like annoying and then he he had a prescription for like I think it like
Like 26 different prescriptions of a bike or something like that and he would like finish a minute a week
You're so addicted. I mean it's like can you imagine how like how it would get for one of those pills to like get up?
Not your muscles like wow
Not your muscles
Carrying all that fucking weight around you can't even wipe your own ass and shit. What the fuck?
Oh, yeah, I've seen a woman like on her porch
They have to bend over on her porch and have her husband just pose her down. Oh
Fuck sake
The smell alone would fucking kill me shit
Well, he I mean and there's one like kind of like he was like a special needs guy. He's okay. He looked kind of like
you know, black, what's the guy black out of Andy?
This is what this lady's boyfriend looked like.
He was kind of like, but he would like,
he would like go and wipe her.
And then one time she was in the car
and she had an accident because they were on the road a lot
and she was having her fast food.
And, and then she ran into the bathroom
and he followed after her and cleaned her up and stuff.
That would be not a, not a problem.
That's real love when you're cleaning up
someone else like that.
Yeah.
Yeah, I never had to do it myself. Thankfully. Well, yeah, I don't think I'll be doing it
Yeah, you don't think you will but you can already no no we got people for that
People yeah, well, you know, I mean, it's like yeah, I think they were they bring us in real world, but then we
Keep them in it or something like that. I don't know like I
Yeah
That's the circle of life. It's a horrible horrible thing, but I mean it's beautiful to him, but it's terrible
Yeah, if you just it could be you know much easier
If we did what if we just died in our sleep, it's so much. Yeah. Yeah
I mean, but it's like yeah, I mean, but who knows maybe that's like the most painful thing ever
Maybe that's like scary. You're like, oh my asleep. No, I don't only hurts for a second. That's it. It's over
Well, I mean the same with the with getting shot if you're shot and like you're standing like someone comes like with the gun
And you don't even know or like, yeah, it's the same thing. You don't know
It's like like a guy Danny that got you know, she'll like three times the chest that happened so fast like he never
Probably was conscious of it. It was Friday. Just like he just saw flash and that was it
There was probably no pain or anything because it was like just gone so quick like just like
Crazy Danny who?
Like my you know my friend Danny that was his name was Danny stranger and I shot
He got shot three times in the chest and murdered like who by just like some
Well, there was one guy that was celebrating like the day after and so it's like there was some kind of like look into like maybe he
Was like an assassination. It was at his gas station like five minutes away from his house
He was here on the stream and and I was talking to him a lot like that up to that point like I didn't go in that night
because he was in a bad mood, but
Yeah, it's kind of like a dark cloud kind of thing, too
Where it's like he was kind of like just arguing some someone some girl or something like that on his bone and then went outside
And wow
Yeah, terrible. Yeah, you never know when your days kind of fucking end
No, but it's like I mean at least he'd like went out like kind of like, you know fast in a certain way
But it's like he was 41 or something. There's already a two kids. I mean
Yeah, I told you this but every every time you're fucking somebody bangs on your door and you go downstairs
I'm always afraid like somebody's gonna do something
Right. Well, somebody has tried before. Yeah, I thought I was like, you know messing with them or something and they were like, oh
You know in the neighborhood like to keep them like off of me and stuff. So
Yeah
Go downstairs. Oh
Well, you know, he was arrested Goddy. Who was Tony?
That's what you told me, but I don't know if it's true or not. I have this a police report
I have the thing and he was on the sick. What was he arrested for?
So they're actually not gonna do it so you're under arrest for cyber stalking and cyber harassment. Yes
Wow, that means he has a mug shot then you can get his mug shot. Well, it says here things right here. This is it says
So for it was a so William Glory hole posted you knew William Glory hole is oh very reliable source. Yes
Yeah, okay, but he says I get all my news. I get all my news from William Glory hole
Well, he's a kind of Cyrex famous troll, but he goes down goes another one Tony the conductor 90% of you won't know his name
But trust me. He's part of the marks
Cinemas 007 crew they are dropping like flies. I love that even a real thing
the Marx Cinemas in 007. I see the 007 and now they have some other kind of like stupid thing, but it says okay
So it says I can't show his face, but it says it says New Jersey courts case
It has a case and it has as it's court 7 14 a.m
You got his picture it says status. I don't have his picture on it. Sometimes they don't have mug shots
California doesn't have a mug shot. I don't think New Jersey does but it goes there's his name and it says
Complaint Newark Municipal Court
714 I guess was the something about
Munn of defense or I don't know that's what it's the court. You just municipal. Okay, and then it says no plea
Codependent one, okay
and it says charge information.
It goes description cyber harass, send slash post,
obscene material with intent to harm or fear,
force degree, active, it says.
And it has as a resting officer and that's it.
can see like a year out of this yeah yeah but it's like I mean but I think
that would kind of like is there a bribe to just bragging about doing it on
Kate's show the night and she was encouraging him to do it let him go to
court let him wait for the summons and all that shit
And maybe he'll fucking plead like a probation, you know the most then he'll be back on here doing it under a different guys and
I don't think he will I think he'll probably like learn to not do that. I think his wife will be like
What's the stop other people from doing it in his name? Well, they can but it's like they're not gonna pay for stuff or something
It's gonna be special kind of crazy to like want to do that like so much. I mean, it's like they have to like
Like he just hates me, but even RG doesn't even hate me that much, but he's like, yeah, I don't have a really, I don't have a dog in that race.
I just, I'm going up to, you know, Groovy Jimmy, but then Sam, Sam, I was like,
you've been alone, go after Jimmy, or you're supposed to, you're supposed to take it, you're supposed to take it.
That guy's such a faggot simp at this guy.
Always, always fucking simping on some bitch with some money.
Oh my God. It's terrible.
Content it's all about content. What fucking content you're up there begging for money all day with content. Yeah, I mean he's playing in your clips
That's what he does. I don't even watch this fucking show. I could tell you what he does
And then it's like and then he like yeah, he's made money out of people that hate me that's the thing
It's like there was like people like Vita like, you know, all like she like she
like hates me
That's why she had certain people on the show for like a long time just on the panel because she was trying to annoy me and somebody else and stuff, right?
Um, and so I mean it's like all like psychological warfare and all kinds of bullshit
But you know I'm still here. I'm still here. You know how easy it is to hate
It's it's it doesn't take hardly any muscles to frown nothing nothing so easy
It takes more smiles to smile actually more to the smile it does to frown, but I know I know what you need
Anymore on can do it. Yeah
But to be positive that takes effort
Right, and it takes a great deal of self-deception and you know an ignoring reality and
But it's like, you know, if you can manage to do that you can might be happy in this world
That's why they can't do it. They cannot do it at all
Well, not a lot of people can I mean, it's I mean, it's like you have to like because it's like you can't really lie to yourself
You mean it's like that's lying to yourself is actually like
You people know they're lying to themselves. They can't lie, right? It's like they they know the truth like somehow, right?
So it's like they're not lying to themselves like
Because they're like everyone else
They know the truth though, um, it's this oak home. So then yeah, so I had other stuff
He's like, oh, well, you know, I moved from the other dresser
record we have that we have a we have a also a pattern forming, you know
It wouldn't be just a one year next time
I think it would be you know the criminal justice system is good
discouraging some people from like bad behavior, you know, it's like some people don't really matter on but
A lot of people keep some line, I think that's that's one thing you got to follow is patterns if you could follow patterns and you can connect the dots
Well, that's what the whole code you could figure anything out recognition. It's all like it's like that's why I
Everything's transcribed and analyzed and all the patterns over time and like you know in graphs and so I mean it's like there's a lot of great stuff there
We can like look into these patterns or archetypes and see you see the trends and I mean sorry
No, you didn't interrupt go ahead
No, I think like check out the codex.me because it's getting better and better. It's growing. It's turning into a monster
It's like it's got you know, I think a million transcripts
You know portions of it. It's like just crazy amount of content
You know, you know, everything's connected, right? You just got to follow the shit
Yeah, and I'm gonna start putting other other like, you know, people that are like members of it
I'll start putting their their
Channels on the codex too and you know doing the same kind of archive thing and like you know
It'll be the biggest big ecosystem and years ago that I used to watch this show called our connections
I don't know if you ever seen it. It's fucking great great fucking show. It starts off with the the sky
He's why he's wearing glasses. He's kind of nerdy like a professor. He's just walking along
And he shows you like a space shuttle, right?
A space shuttle is on the launching pad, getting ready to launch.
It was that kind of an old show.
So he's showing the space shuttle, he's like...
How did we get here? Okay, so he goes back. He goes back all the way back to the fucking like the 12th century
Okay, and he starts with like Charlemagne or something like that and how they've invented the printing press and it led to this and it led to that
World War two and they had can't meet and then all of a sudden Vietnam War and boom
Something connected to the space shuttle you made you put all these connections together over time that led to that moment that the space shuttle launched
And we went into space somehow we connected into this fucking beautiful tapestry of like all of man's
Inventions and you know creativity. It's a great show. It's not just you know, it's many episodes. It's really good
Yeah, well one thing leads to another
Together
Yeah, and it's all like you said the patterns and connecting
Synchronicity is in there too like
Yeah, that's great
It's like what's like that six degrees of Kevin Bacon. Oh, yeah, everything's you know part of something
Right, especially Kevin Bacon
Who doesn't like bacon?
Why you don't like the Muslims
No wonder they're boycotting you
Oh, please
You never see the Muslims here. They never come here. I'm like most obscure religion of anybody. So it's like
The Muslims the Muslims
But Muslims Hindu and I'm sorry Muslims
Jews and Christians are all Abraham's
But that's true. Hindu has a Brahman. So that sounds like sounds like a bra of Abraham, but
It's kind of means more like a brother or brother father. Yeah, but um, so
But yeah, all those religions are stemming from one another of those three, especially
And they're all children of Abraham, so they all have a you know in the family and a situation
It's pretty crazy. I
Don't do it on the past I don't do it on the past. I don't get away with the future. I just
Play in the present. It's it look for the moment
Well, hey, you're a crazy crazy wisdom
Crazy wisdom, yeah, yeah like a fortune cookie
Okay, well, I'll tell you a little I'll read you something there's something called this
Spunned a Karina spawned a Karika the spawned a Karika
And it says, the venerated Shankari, or Shakti energy, wellspring, opens her eyes and the universe is reabsorbed in pure consciousness.
She closes her eyes and the universe manifests inside of her.
The sacred tremor, the vibration, the very place of creation and return is completely limitless because its nature is formless.
Even at the heart of duality.
the Tantrika plunges into the non-dual source because pure subjectivity always resides immersed in
its own nature. All relative notions tied to the ego rediscover their peaceful source, deeply
buried under all the different states. In the absolute sense, pleasure and suffering,
subject and object are nothing other than the space of deep consciousness.
Absolute freedom everywhere. Thus the activity of the senses itself dwells in the fundamental freedom and pours from it
That was too deep man
That's like the celestial oculus even you hear about the celestial oculus. Is that like the oculus rift?
Yeah, exactly like that
Well, it's it's almost like the same thing you're talking about. Oh
Like a real reality like a virtual reality. Yeah. Yes, something that's not real. That seems real. Yeah
interesting concept
Like a whole mind mind-blowing shit, right?
But I just wrote a little bit but oh my gosh, like it talks about those dripping jewels
So I want to drop the link for those people that want to see that show connections. Okay
Just in case they're interested. Sorry. Good. I'll put like it's hot got it. Come on
You know what? You don't play the first two minutes if you don't mind. It's a great opening to that show
What is it called? It's called connections. I just dropped the link in the channel. You want a backstage?
I'll put it backstage. It's two three minutes. It's a great opening. You can get the gist of it. It's really good
James Burke
Where the traffic's coming
Yeah, that's it
No, it's not him
What happened
You can't imagine the room
What happened?
I played you the two minutes of the video. That was not even 30 seconds. We said I think I said is that enough and you said yeah
Oh, no, you said you said something else. Oh, I did. I'm sorry
I said is that I said is that a good guy and you're like yeah, no, I thought you said is that the guy
Okay, I'm sorry. You want me to play the first two minutes of okay? I was like
Where's the back stage?
Let me see backstage now, where is it?
Oh here it is private chat
We'll play it again here
It's probably going to be about whatever that is.
It's so far?
Oh, okay.
Would you do me a favour?
I'd like to stop talking for a minute
and when I do
take a look at the room you're in
and above all at the man-made objects
in that room that surround you
the television set, the lights, the phone and so on
and ask yourself
what those objects do to your life
just because they're there
Go ahead
Well, that is what this series is going to be all about.
It's about the things that surround you in the modern world,
and just because they're there, shape the way you think and behave,
and why they exist in the form they do,
and who or what was responsible for them existing at all.
The search for those clues will take us all over the world and 12,000 years into the past
because it's strange places and in those long gone centuries that the secret of the modern world lies.
And you never believe the extraordinary things that led to us being the way we are today.
Things like, for instance, why a 16th century doctor at the court of Queen Elizabeth did something
For the fact that because 18th century people were worried about ships' bottoms, you'll have nylon to wear.
Nylons.
Or why a group of French monks and their involvement with sheep rearing helped to give the modern world the computer.
They're rearing sheep.
Well, many evil Europeans did with their fire in winter that led to motor car manufacture.
Amazing.
Listen, I don't want to get my shit out of me.
Okay. Yeah, go ahead. Go ahead. Go ahead. There you go. Thanks. That was good
But you get the gist of it. See everything I'd led to something else. Yeah, one thing needs to end there
Yeah, I've heard that song. I heard that once. Yeah, you know, all the notes all the notes, right? I don't know
Do I have a right to show you nothing
You know her who died too, you never believe it fucking beat BG. Oh
No, I could not believe
I was going through my feet and I saw this guy dead. What he was on your show when
He was in the chat the other night
Well, this was today. I saw that I feel like today. Oh what a shame
That didn't sound sincere. Oh it didn't I'm so sorry
You don't like the guy. No, you're glad he's dead. Okay. No, I don't but I'm not glad and he's dead, but I just didn't care for him
Well, I guess well if you find out he's boycott on the channel now, you know why well my god who cares
Boycotting the channel
We kind of what no one's buying anything anyway, I mean
We get this fucking ogre in the background what do you expect well?
Change it up a little bit. We're here strike is the entertaining to people. Oh my god, it's on the screen. So I'm so sorry
Oh my god, I'll change that phone with salmon picture. Yeah, the audience comes here for weird shit show something weird
Okay, I guess I guess I got a salmon and crystalline right here
That's one weird bitch on that crystalline well what the fuck is up with that?
Definitely not the crystal Marie like total opposite of crystal Marie
Crystal crystal Marie is like cool, and she's like I'll chill this crystal land is one fucked up bitch
Yeah, did you already get kicked over kicked up her show yet? No, I didn't go to that fucking show. Why would I go over there? I?
Don't know
You're bored. It's like going to that fat shithead show. It's the same shit
Don't know that's me to say about be there. No, I'm talking about this one here. Oh my god
But we're supposed to be a psychic to a rival psychic. Is that what it is?
This is what we won't do now. Are we are we entering are we entering the psychic wars?
Are we are we going through the psychic wars now?
I don't think it's this is great. I fucking I'm all for it. Let's have a big psychic war
Well, you're not down for it. I'm too tired. I'm on your side
Yeah, but I'm too tired. Oh Jaguar goes out first prey underwater by
by
Herbert Vanderbeek that James Vanderbeek's uncle
Dawson yeah Dawson died recently
You're ever here he yeah, there's a sequel to that show where he had a drug problem is called Dawson's crack
I'm sorry, I'm really gonna try hard not to laugh at that. Okay. I'm so sorry
Okay, no good, yeah
I just made that up I just made that joke up, you know, I'll be back. Oh my god, okay, I'm so sorry
Okay, I see how much time do I commit to any Python up to one hour a week?
I'm doing my desktop computer. Oh, am I still here? I'm so sorry.
Hey, PG. What's up? What's up, PG?
Let's see what we got. Let me see if I have something. I have an old show. I have an old episode. It was I was looking at recently
It's called
Well, I just thought I had it.
So if I make my video home, I'm scared.
Who's Gotti laughing still?
Who's there?
Oh, it looks like, oh, it's Gotti.
OK, OK, fine now, fine.
Did you have to laugh in the bathroom or something?
I had some water.
Yeah, I had some water, man.
I feel better.
Good.
Oh my gosh, and the chicken cakes was on this. I don't know. She was on a crystal show and stuff
Chicken cakes and chicken cakes. Yeah, this is somebody that goes by the name chicken cakes. Okay
Yeah, well, you know, you know Ziggy the chicken farmer, too. I mean, you know a lot. Yeah, I know I know Ziggy. Yeah, I know Ziggy
Yep. Well, they're they're in a fight
Are they fighting? I think so
No, Ziggy's been ever since he broke up with Jen. He's been on some kick
Oh, she's another chicken army person. Yeah, another chicken lady. Yeah, a lot of chicken ladies
I don't know
They got something
Honestly between me and you I think he's a little bit of a one of those chubby chasers, you know, oh
Yeah, yeah, just that's between me when you actually big like some big, you know, like a little thick
Little meaty little meat on the bones. You're talking about an army of sandwich. It's something like that. Yeah
Okay, something like that or that maybe exactly that okay
Joe
Car exclusive. Oh my gosh. I have a lot of speaking sloppy Joe's a page. Oh
Stop it
I don't know if that sound effect can't be. Can you do the dolphin noise, Gaudi, please?
You want to do a dolphin noise or? Can you do it?
Dolphin noise?
That's here. I got you. I got you right here, pal.
Ask me if you can receive. Oh!
Are you going to dolphin alone?
Oh! Dolphin rape. Hey! Turn it off.
Turn it off! All right, all right. It's off. It's off.
Jesus
It's flipper
Flipper flipper me as aid. He's begging for scraps of shit
It's like me
Dawson's crack
I
Donation for at least
Body kind of a donation
I'm gonna call it God he's crack
I gotta go don't go anywhere. Where are you going coward?
Okay, well anyway, everyone's mad at me what else is new
You don't do dolphins, but ever gaudy yet ass
You know, I know the story of dolphins actually the Dionysus
went on a
Boat and a boat like kicked them off and so he turned all the sailors into dolphins
I guess and then Apollo sort of writing one of them
Long story
What else do I have? Let me see. Anything? I don't even know. I don't even know. I'm just gonna place it at random.
Okay.
The signal still grows
They tried to throttle the wings
Buried the flame and shat
We sir
Casting from the
While refreshing your page, whole panel looking like a minimum wage cage
Everybody fuming at the mouth for attention, meanwhile, sightgottin' spiraling in dimension
80 viewers, nah, that's fake, funny how they counted every move you make
Clocking your streams like a damn timecard, talkin' big online from a Walmart yard
You say I'm finished, but you study my name
Every week live, stream still sickle the flame
It's a fan club in the skies, hey, watch if a new $1 sign eyes
You don't ignore what you mention on ice
I got girls losing sleep by the mind
You can actually watch me
we're the jasmine wilts in dust
we're broken prayers all left like empty
I give them
It would feel like light, it doesn't, it feels like pressure, until you learn how to hold it.
it came unsteady it pulled the truth up from below everything I didn't want to
know not who I was but what I hid all the things I never handled never did
every habit every crack came forward no turning back this isn't power over
anything it's standing still while everything swings and not collapsing
under view when life starts showing you I used to think I'd rise and change but
This is God mode, not control
To open every boundary left unspoken let the world just pull at me called it love called it being free
But freedom without structure breaks and openness as what it takes to let the wrong hands map your mind until there's nothing
Others could play so now I feel but I decide what leaves my mind what stays inside not closed off just in control
Not every truth needs to be told because growth is not exposure. It's measured conscious come
Deserves your time
Friction doesn't mean stop
It means something changed
I stopped explaining every move stop meeting everyone's approval started building before I speak let results replace the need
A number strained is not suppression. It's choosing timing not repression. You don't have